Guide to the Bernard and Jewel Bellush Papers WAG.030
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Interview and AFSCME Local Files, 1948-1984.
  - Locals: General, 1957-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - General: Leaflets, Newsletters, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Maritime Port Council, 1961-1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Membership By Locals, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Local 154, NYC Employees, 1957-1965 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Local 237, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Local 237, Teamsters v. Local 1783, Housing Authority, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Local 299, Recreational Employees, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Local 371, Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), 1965 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Local 371, SSEU, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Local 371, SSEU, 1967-1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Local 371, SSEU Strike, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Local 372, Board of Education, 1961-1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Local 372, Board of Education, 1968-1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Local 372, Board of Education, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Local 372, School Lunch Aides, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Local 374, NY/Brooklyn Botanical Garden, 1957-1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Local 376, Parks Department, 1967-1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Local 384, CUNY, 1957-1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Local 442, Subway Supervisors, 1961-1964 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Local 824, Laborers, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Local 924-376, Laborers, Undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Local 983, Motor Vehicle Operator's Strike, 1956-1967 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Local 1070, Judicial Conference, 1961-1965 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Local 1087, Bureau of Community Education, Prevailing Rate, 1956-1965 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Local 1113, Finance Employees, 1958-1966 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Local 1306, Museum of Natural History, 1956-1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Local 1321-1482, Queensborough Public Library, 1966-1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Local 1320, Public Works, 1957-1963 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Local 1396, Triborough Bridge and Tunnel, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Local 1407, Accountants, 1962-1964 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Local 1501, New York Zoo, 1956-1961 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Local 1503, Metropolitan Museum, 1959-1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Local 1549, CWA Raid, 1965-1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Local 1597, Custodial Employees, 1960-1966 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Series VI: Chapter Drafts.
  - Chapter Headings, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Early Years, to 1950, Chapter 1, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - We Have Faith in You, Chapter 2, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Who Built This Union, Robert Moses, Chapter 3, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining, Not Collective Begging, Chapter 4, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Never Again in Awe of Power, Chapter 5, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - You Can Fight City Hall, Chapter 7, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hospital Elections, Chapter 8, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Collective Bargaining: Seat of Power, Chapter 9, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gotbaum Takes Command, Chapter 10, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Inside Union Bureaucracy, Chapter 11, draft, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Political MachineUnion Made, Chapter 12, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Operation Price Watch, former Chapter 12, draft, Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Political Participation, Chapter 13, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Learn, Baby Learn, Chapter 14, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Expanding Union Services, Chapter 15, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - In the Shadow of the Crisis, Chapter 16, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - The Fiscal Crisis - Threat and Response, Chapter 17, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The Contest of Power, Chapter 18, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)